Oh, my gosh!
Ha! Ha!
Sorry I edited it up.
I don't know.
It's all delicious!
Hello everyone!
I'm Hinano Uemura from Hyuhizaka 46!
Where am I right now?
That's right, the correct answer is
Ta-da!
Do you see Kitasanjo Station?
I'm at Kita Sanjo Station.
Today is my day off from filming for a TV drama
I thought I'd take a stroll around Sanjo.
I'm turning on YouTube.
Let's go!
It's a beautiful day today!
It's a beautiful day, isn't it?
Ehehehehe!
Well, here we are!
Ta-da!
Stage edge river!
Spice Laboratory, or something like that... It's in the anime!
It's very close to the station!
Wow! Look at this! It's a beautiful day!
It's great!
Thank you very much for watching.
Wow, it's a beautiful day today!
Near the stage-engineer.
I like to say Mr. Machiyama
Just in between
There is a ski board bench like this
You can see it in one of the most impressive scenes in the anime
I sat on it.
Ski bench
Today
Look at this.
I brought a DIY bag.
Why don't you come and take a look?
Why don't you come take a look?
I'm walking to the shopping street now.
I found some nice soda pop earlier and bought it.
If I open it here.
I'm afraid I'd overflow.
If I find a good place, I'll open it and drink it there.
I'll open it and drink it there.
I love summer!
I'm in Niigata for the first time.
I'm coming to Niigata for a month by myself.
I'm a little far away from here.
That's right.
When I was first told I'd be going to Niigata for a drama shoot.
I was very anxious because it was my first experience.
But when I came to Niigata, I found it to be very
It was so warm.
The people are so warm and kind.
I thought it was a very nice town.
After I heard about this drama
I watched the DIY anime.
Oh, wow!Oh, wow.
Oh, oh, a wrapped cab
A DIY wrapped cab just passed by!
I'm sorry, I'm so excited.
I think it's coming soon, right?
Soon, maybe.
The shopping street is getting closer.
Here it comes!
This is where we do our dromatic style!
Michiichi!
This is a very impressive scene in the anime!
I think this is the place where people say "Doichi" in Japanese.
Next spot
Heading to the next spot.
There are so many overhead!
The name of the bridge is written here.
We've arrived at the stone bridge.
This is where we're all walking at the opening.
This is where we're walking.
Let's take a break here.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no!
What am I doing?
What are they doing?
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
A little this way.
The kilometer is 7.0 km
This did not finish.
If I don't finish this, I give up and give up. Me.
I'm going.
Three, two, one!
Three, two, one.
I'm on it.
Looks like we can go.
It's gone!
What?
Yeah!
We're there, guys!
I heard about this.
Oh, my God! How long was I on for?
I think we were on for about 20 minutes.
The sun's getting nice now.
Thank you for your time.
My Ramune Opening Ceremony
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Delicious!
Thanks for your time.
I'm heading to a spot in Peña Quisquey.
It's just around the corner from here again.
I believe there is a Anegi Fruit
Here's the fruit at Anegi Fruit
Sandwich
It's a famous fruit store, like Mr. Fruit.It's a famous store like Mr. Fruit
It also appears in the anime DIY!
We are about to arrive at Anegi Fruits.
I see it!
We have arrived at Anegi Fruits!
Oh, there is a panel of Shi-chan!
Shi-chan!
Hello.
Thank you for taking care of us today.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome.
Thank you very much.
It's a very nice store.
I went to the fruit sandwich corner.
I came here as fast as I could.
Like this
Anegi Fruit's fruit sandwiches
It's afternoon and they are very popular
It's sold out!
Each character ate like this!
It comes with a pop-up that introduces
You can enjoy the same fruit sandwiches as the characters
the same fruit sandwiches as the delicious characters.
It's a nice point, isn't it?
An essential part of the life and death pilgrimage
Anegi fruit sandwiches!
Which one shall I choose?
Ah!
Strawberry and banana made with strawberry cream!
I think I'll have this one today.
There's 48 yen left.
Yes, thank you.
It's pink strawberry cream with strawberries and bananas
I'd like to have a fruit sandwich.
There are so many!
What shall we eat?
Let's eat.
Delicious!
The fruit is sweet!
I just ate a strawberry
Strawberry
Just the right amount of tartness and cream sweetness.
It's really a perfect balance.
I'm ashamed to admit that I did a food report.
Fruit Sandwich
Fruit sandwich
Fruit sandwiches!
I want to tell you how delicious it is! I don't know what to do!
The fruit itself is so delicious.
the bread, the cream...
I don't know...
I don't know.
Everything is delicious.
I think it's a well-loved taste.
I've been so focused on this drama
I haven't been in touch with the members much.
But this morning, I got a call from Mikko Takahashi.
We had a nice conversation.
Shiho-san and Mirei-san are also very worried about me.
Shiho-san and Mirei-san were also very concerned and contacted me.They contacted me with great concern.
We feel the love of the members as we shoot the film.
Joasself, who will be playing the role this time
She is a messed up girl.
She makes a lot of mistakes.
But she tries her best in everything she does.
But she tries her best in everything and grows up little by little
I love her so much.
She's my favorite character.
I'm really happy to be able to play the role of Self-chan.
There were many things I couldn't do very well myself
I was often depressed because I didn't do so well.
But while playing the role of Self-chan
I've come to think that it's okay.
I'm really glad that I was able to come across this work.
I'm really happy to have met you.
Thank you for the food.
Fruit sandwiches!
I finished it!
So fast! I want to eat more!
It was delicious!
This is how it went today.
We made a pilgrimage to the holy land of anime DIY
Finally, the Drama DIY!
It's going to start on July 4.
I think it's going to be a very nice work
I would be very happy if you could watch it!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching until the end!
Hinatazaka Channel
Please subscribe to our channel
and "Good" button!
See you soon!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!